const questions = [
    {
        question: "1: Which is the Biggest Planet in the Solar System",
        options: ["A: Earth", "B: Mars", "C: Venus", "D: Jupiter"],
        correctAnswerIndex: 3
    },
    {
        question: "2: What is the capital of France?",
        options: ["A: London", "B: Berlin", "C: Madrid", "D: Paris"],
        correctAnswerIndex: 3
    },
    {
        question: "3: Which planet is known as the Red Planet",
        options: ["A: Earth", "B: Mars", "C: Venus", "D: Jupiter"],
        correctAnswerIndex: 1
    },
    {
        question: "4: Who wrote the play Romeo and Juliet?",
        options: ["A: Charles Dickens", "B: William Shakespeare", "C: Jane Austen", "D: F. Scott Fitzgerald"],
        correctAnswerIndex: 1
    },
    {
        question: "5: What is the largest mammal in the world?",
        options: ["A: Elephant", "B: Giraffe", "C: Blue Whale", "D: Lion"],
        correctAnswerIndex: 2
    },
    {
        question: "6: Which gas do plants absorb from the atmosphere?",
        options: ["A: Oxygen", "B: Nitrogen", "C: Carbon Dioxide", "D: Hydrogen"],
        correctAnswerIndex: 2
    },
    {
        question: "7: In which year did Christopher Columbus discover America",
        options: ["A: 1492", "B: 1607", "C: 1776", "D: 1812"],
        correctAnswerIndex: 0
    },
    {
        question: "8: Which country is famous for its tulips and windmills?",
        options: ["A: France", "B: Italy", "C: Netherlands", "D: Spain"],
        correctAnswerIndex: 2
    },
    {
        question: "9: What is the largest organ in the human body?",
        options: ["A: Heart", "B: Brain", "C: Liver", "D: Skin"],
        correctAnswerIndex: 3
    },
    {
        question: "10: What is the chemical formula for water?",
        options: ["A: CO2", "B: H2O", "C: NaCl", "D: O2"],
        correctAnswerIndex: 1
    },
    // Add more questions here
];